http://www.sccba.com/?page=privacy

privacy policy - Santa Clara County Bar Association
Print Page   |   Contact Us   |   Sign In   |   Join Us
directories
Alternative Dispute ResolutionJudicial ProfilesPublic Attorney Directory
Who We Are
bench/bar relationshipblogs
legal flashpresident's message blogblog search
center for ethics & professionalism
code of professionalismethics forumethics blogethics opinionsprofessional lawyer of the yearprofessionalism committee
governing documents
by-lawscode of professionalismmission statement
leadership
board of trusteesexecutive committeeSCCBA CommitteesSCCBA Sectionspast president's message (archive)
sccba member benefits
room rentalcareer developmentcontinuing educationmarketingnetworkingpractice toolsinsurance products
staffjoin us
practice development
browse legal linkscreate a public directory listingjoin the lawyer referral serviceprofessional development
enhance your profilejoin a groupmy cle managermy cle manager - about
research with casemakersearch judicial profilesvisit the career center
get involved
annual programsfind a group
committees
appellate courtscivil practiceconference of delegatesdiversityfederal courtsfee arbitrationfinancejudiciarylaw related educationlawyer referral serviceprofessionalism
sections
ai, robotics & high technology lawalternative dispute resolutionbarristerscriminal lawenvironmental lawfamily lawimmigration lawinsurance lawlabor & employment lawrainbow bar: LGBTQ+ attorneys & alliesreal property & business lawwomen lawyers
meetings calendar
judicial assessmentprofessional programssccba initiatives
diversitypro bonoprofessionalism
selection of 2019 trustees/officersvolunteer opportunitiesjoin a section or committee
cle & events
calendarcle online catalogmcle compliancemeetings calendarmy cle manager
find a lawyer
Site Search
Search »
Edit This Favorite
Name:
Category:
Share:
Yes
No, Keep Private
privacy policy
Share
|
Website Visitor’s Personal Information: Privacy Policy
We are committed to maintain and respect the privacy of visitors to our website and to safeguard any personal information provided by a visitor in accessing and/or using services offered through the website.
These policies are as follows:
Our Web server automatically recognizes only the visitor’s domain name (where possible), but not the e-mail address.We collect only the information a visitor may provide voluntarily to us when completing a transaction on the website; this information is used only in relation to providing that visitor the services the visitor is requesting or has purchased.The information we collect is not shared with other organizations for commercial or non-commercial purposes. If you do not want to receive email from us in the future, please let us know by sending email to us at info@sccba.com and telling us that you do not want to receive email from the SCCBA. Persons who supply us with their email or telephone numbers online may receive email or telephone contact from us with information regarding services they have requested online.
The SCCBA does not sell, rent or lease its email lists to third parties. The LACBA may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your personal email information is not transferred to the third party.
The SCCBA may access and/or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on the SCCBA or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of the SCCBA; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the SCCBA services or members of the public.
The SCCBA is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers and the expiration date when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.
If you choose to visit SCCBA.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of California. If you have any concern about privacy at LACBA.org, please contact us through the email address above with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it.
more
Latest News
9/14/20202020 Judges' Night4/2/2020A New Legal Reality3/5/2020Women’s History Month
more
Calendar
10/15/2020Issues facing the Court of Appeal in the time of COVID10/19/2020What Business and Real Property Practitioners Need to Know About The New Small Business10/21/2020Women Lawyers Executive Committee -October 2020
Recent Recognitions
Constance L. Carpenter2018 Pro Bono Lawyer of the YearJenn M. Protas2018 Diversity Award
